<?xml version="1.0"?>
<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><CreaDate>20250217</CreaDate><CreaTime>11453700</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce><ModDate>20250217</ModDate><ModTime>16300200</ModTime><scaleRange><minScale>150000000</minScale><maxScale>5000</maxScale></scaleRange><ArcGISProfile>ItemDescription</ArcGISProfile></Esri><tool name="ClassifyPixelsUsingDeepLearning" displayname="Classify Pixels Using Deep Learning" toolboxalias="Toolbox for post-processing deep learning results" xmlns=""><arcToolboxHelpPath>c:\program files\arcgis\pro\Resources\Help\gp</arcToolboxHelpPath><parameters><param name="in_raster" displayname="Input Raster" type="Required" direction="Input" datatype="Raster Dataset or Raster Layer or Mosaic Dataset or Image Service or Map Server or Map Server Layer or Internet Tiled Layer or Folder or Feature Layer or Feature Class" expression="in_raster"/><param name="model_definition" displayname="Model Definition" type="Required" direction="Input" datatype="File" expression="model_definition"/><param name="out_classified_raster" displayname="Output Classified Raster" type="Required" direction="Output" datatype="Raster Dataset" expression="out_classified_raster"/><param name="processing_geometry" displayname="Processing Geometry" type="Required" direction="Input" datatype="Feature Class or Feature Layer" expression="processing_geometry"/><param name="arguments" displayname="Arguments" type="Optional" direction="Input" datatype="Value Table" expression="{Name {Value};Name {Value}...}"><dialogReference>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;"The information from the Model Definition parameter will be used to populate this parameter. "&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;        "These arguments vary, depending on the model architecture. The following are supported model arguments for models trained in ArcGIS. "&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;        "ArcGIS pretrained models and custom deep learning models may have additional arguments that the tool supports.\n"&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;        "• batch_size—The number of image tiles processed in each step of the model inference. This depends on the memory of your graphics card. The argument is available for all model architectures.\n"&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;        "• direction—The image is translated from one domain to another. Options are AtoB and BtoA. The argument is only available for the CycleGAN architecture. For more information about this argument, see How CycleGAN works.\n"&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;        "• merge_policy—The policy for merging augmented predictions. Available options are mean, max, and min. This is only applicable when test time augmentation is used. The argument is available for the MultiTaskRoadExtractor and ConnectNet architectures. If IsEdgeDetection is present in the model's .emd file, the BDCNEdgeDetector, HEDEdgeDetector, and MMSegmentation architectures are also available.\n"&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;        "• n_timestep—The number of time steps that will be used. The default is 200. It can be increased and decreased based on the quality of generations. The argument is only supported for the Super Resolution with SR3 backbone model.\n"&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;        "• padding—The number of pixels at the border of image tiles from which predictions are blended for adjacent tiles. To smooth the output while reducing artifacts, increase the value. The maximum value of the padding can be half the tile size value. The argument is available for all model architectures.\n"&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;        "• predict_background—Specifies whether the background class will be classified. If true, the background class is also classified. The argument is available for UNET, PSPNET, DeepLab, MMSegmentation, and SAMLoRA.\n"&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;        "• return_probability_raster—Specifies whether the output will be a probability raster. If true, the output will be a probability raster. If false, the output will be a binary classified raster. The default is false. If ArcGISLearnVersion is 1.8.4 or later in the model's .emd file, the MultiTaskRoadExtractor and ConnectNet architectures are available. If ArcGISLearnVersion is 1.8.4 or later and IsEdgeDetection is present in the model's .emd file, the BDCNEdgeDetector, HEDEdgeDetector, and MMSegmentation architectures are also available.\n"&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;        "• sampling_type—The type of sampling that will be used. Two types of sampling are available: ddim and ddpm. The default is ddim, which generates results in fewer time steps compared to ddpm. The argument is only supported for the Super Resolution with SR3 backbone model.\n"&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;        "• schedule—An optional string that sets the type of schedule. The default schedule is the same as the model it was trained on. The argument is only supported for the Super Resolution with SR3 backbone model.\n"&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;        "• test_time_augmentation—Specifies whether test time augmentation will be performed while predicting. If true, predictions of flipped and rotated variants of the input image will be merged into the final output. The argument is available for UNET, PSPNET, DeepLab, HEDEdgeDetector, BDCNEdgeDetector, ConnectNet, MMSegmentation, Multi-Task Road Extractor, and SAMLoRA.\n"&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;        "• tile_size—The width and height of image tiles into which the imagery will be split for prediction. The argument is only available for the CycleGAN architecture.\n"&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;        "• thinning—Specifies whether predicted edges will be thinned or skeletonized. Options are True and False. If IsEdgeDetection is present in the model's .emd file, the BDCNEdgeDetector, HEDEdgeDetector, and MMSegmentation architectures are available.\n"&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;        "• threshold—The predictions that have a confidence score higher than this threshold are included in the result. The allowed values range from 0 to 1.0. If ArcGISLearnVersion is 1.8.4 or later in the model's .emd file, the MultiTaskRoadExtractor and ConnectNet architectures are available. If ArcGISLearnVersion is 1.8.4 or later and IsEdgeDetection is present in the model's .emd file, the BDCNEdgeDetector, HEDEdgeDetector, and MMSegmentation architectures are also available."&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;    &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</dialogReference></param></parameters></tool><dataIdInfo><idCitation><resTitle>Classify Pixels Using Deep Learning</resTitle></idCitation></dataIdInfo><distInfo><distributor><distorFormat><formatName>ArcToolbox Tool</formatName></distorFormat></distributor></distInfo><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="005"/></mdHrLv><mdDateSt Sync="TRUE">20250217</mdDateSt></metadata>
